//creating an array and passing the number ,quietions,options and answers

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the day before Mardi Gras called?",
        answer: "Lundi Gras",
        options:[
            "Luni Toons",
            "Moana",
            "Ladis Gras",
            "Lundi Gras"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What day comes after Mardi Gras?",
        answer: "Ash Wednesday",
        options:[
            "Ash Monday",
            "Ash Wednesday",
            "Ladis Day",
            "Lundi Gras day"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "When was the earliest known carnival celebration?",
        answer: "1294",
        options:[
            "1294",
            "1889",
            "1945",
            "1900"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the signature Mardi Gras dessert?",
        answer: "King Cake",
        options:[
            "Sweet Tooth Cake",
            "White Cake",
            "King Cake",
            "Queen Cake"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What are the groups that organize New Orleans Mardi Gras parades called?",
        answer: "Krewes",
        options:[
            "Dudes",
            "Pesants",
            "Knights",
            "Krewes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What does purple signify during Mardi Gras?",
        answer: "Justice",
        options:[
            "Love",
            "Peace",
            "Justice",
            "Seranetiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the most popular food for Shrove Tuesday?",
        answer: "Pancakes",
        options:[
            "Pancakes",
            "Pizza",
            "Shrimp",
            "Pork"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many times have Mardi Gras parades been canceled in New Orleans?",
        answer: "13",
        options:[
            "13",
            "9",
            "101",
            "17"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "On average, how many people typically visit New Orleans for Mardi Gras every year?",
        answer: "1.4 million",
        options:[
            "2 million",
            "800,000",
            "10 million",
            "1.4 million"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the traditional phrase used to request beads during Mardi Gras?",
        answer: "Throw me something, mister!",
        options:[
            "Such is Life",
            "Burn me with an enemy",
            "Throw me something, mister!",
            "To Life!"
        ]
    },
]